

### **PERSONAL**

- Name
  Sarra Mousselmal
- ★ Address Tiaret, Ut, Fd 14003 tieret
- Phone number 0793157532
- Date of birth 08-08-2001
- Place of birth SOUGUEUR
- Female

  Nationality

**Gender** 

- Algeria **†∔ Marital status**
- Single

  Driving licence
- Website https://github.com/SarraMsl
- LinkedIn

  https://www.linkedin.com/in/saramoussalmal-208497219

### **INTERESTS**

- Design
- Programmation
- Reading

#### **LANGUAGES**

English  $\star \star$ French  $\star \star$ Arabic  $\star \star \star$ 

# SARRA MOUSSELMAL

My name is Sarra Mousselmal, I'm from Algeria, I'm 21 years old, I have a bachelor's degree in computer science from the university ibn Khaldun Algeria, concerning my work experience I have over 3 years of experience as a Web developer I have passion for responsive website design. Implemented new responsive website approach Deeply knowledgeable in a wide variety of computer languages, including HTML5, JavaScript and PHP and understands principles and techniques of initial website construction I'm excited to take on some larger projects. I want to continue to develop my skills as a web developer and to prove that I'm able to take on multiple projects at one time. Furthermore, I think the scale and importance of these projects can push me to develop professionally and can help me meet my full potential.



# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

Jul 2019 - Jul 2021 Professor and administrator

Cultural Center Muhammad Ali Dabouz, Ghardaia

Cultural Center Muhammad Ali Dabouz

Jul 2022 - Aug 2022 Informatics trainer

Qabas, Ghardaia

I have worked as a C language and algorithms instructor as well as a

mathematics teacher

Jul 2021 - Sep 2022 Software developer

Office of IT Development, Metlili

I worked as web front-end developer



# **EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS**

Sep 2018 - Jul 2019 Baccalaureate

Majdoub Zakaria, Sougueur

Technical Baccalaureate Mention good mechanical engineering

Sep 2019 - Jul 2022 Bachelor's

University of iben khaldoun, Tiaret

Bachelor's degree in Information Systems (class B)

Sep 2021 - Present Senior technician

Hassiba Benbouali Center for Vocational Training and Apprenticeship.,

Algeria

2021-2022 Senior technician in Computer Science

Option:Networks and information systems

Sep 2022 - Present Master's

Iben Khaldoun, Tiaret

Option: Software engineer



### **SKILLS**

Data base manager sql databases

front-end web

Php ★★★★

solve various computer problems, install progra Algorithm \*\*\*\* communication protocols  $\star\star\star\star\star$ Illustrator Design **MS Office**  $\star\star\star\star\star$ \*\*\*\* **Microsoft windows** \*\*\*\* **Technical Support Troubleshooting Software Maintenance Windows** 



## **COURSES**



Jul 2022 - Present

### Google UX design

Coursera

path to a career in UX design. In this program, you'll learn in-demand skills that will have you job-ready in less than 6 months.



# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- -Website of Money Transfer. (Participation in the United Nations Solutions Challenge 05/04/2022)-google developers students clubs Received a 50 Top project Badge and a Certificate of Participation from Google.
- -A website for the University of Ghardaia, an intermediary between thed aministration and the professor to submit and solved the complaint.
- -A ranking site for undergraduate students in the Master 1 exams of the Computer Science major.
- -A website to preview the applied work of students by the professor at Tiaret University.
- -A website to archive student developments during their university career and during the work phase.